ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- General Correspondence N. L. and E. W. Kruysman, Inc., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 78)
- General Correspondence "L" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 79)
- General Correspondence "L" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 80)
- General Correspondence Labor, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 81)
- General Correspondence Labor Headline News, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 82)
- General Correspondence Labor-Personnel Index, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 83)
- General Correspondence The Labour Court - Dublin, Ireland, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 84)
- General Correspondence Land Economics, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 85)
- General Correspondence Landis, Elizabeth (Mrs.), 1950 (Box 16, Folder 86)
- General Correspondence Individual Landsberger, Henry, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 87)
- General Correspondence Lara, Raul, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 88)
- General Correspondence League for Industrial Democracy, Inc., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 89)
- General Correspondence League of Women Voters of N.Y., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 90)
- General Correspondence Individual Leenhouts, Hugh D., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 91)
- General Correspondence The Legislative Index Company, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 92)
- General Correspondence Individual Senator Herbert H. Lehman, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 93)
- General Correspondence Legislative Reference Library, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 94)
- General Correspondence LeTourneau Technical Institute of Texas, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 95)
- General Correspondence Individual, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 96)
- General Correspondence Library Association of Portland, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 97)
- General Correspondence London School of Economics, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 98)
- General Correspondence The London Times, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 99)
- General Correspondence University of Louisville, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 100)
- General Correspondence Individual Lundberg, Donald E., 1950 (Box 16, Folder 101)
- General Correspondence "M" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 102)
- General Correspondence "M" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 103)
- General Correspondence The M B Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 104)
- General Correspondence McGill University (Box 16, Folder 105)
- General Correspondence McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 106)
- General Correspondence Machinists, International Association of, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 107)
- General Correspondence Management House, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 108)
- General Correspondence Magnafile Company, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 109)
- General Correspondence Management Methods, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 110)
- General Correspondence School of Business Manhattan College, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 111)
- General Correspondence Manufacturers Assn. of Syracuse, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 112)
- General Correspondence The March of Labor, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 113)
- General Correspondence - Individual Marning, Karl G., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 114)
- General Correspondence A. N. Marquis Company, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 115)
- General Correspondence Individual Marvin, Richard, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 116)
- General Correspondence Maryland University, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 117)
- General Correspondence Mass. Civic Education Project, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 118)
- General Correspondence Massachusetts State Library, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 119)
- General Correspondence University of Massachusetts, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 120)
- General Correspondence University of Massachusetts, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 121)
- General Correspondence Individual Miss Yachiyo Matouchi, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 122)
- General Correspondence Individual Murray Melbin, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 123)
- General Correspondence Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 124)
- General Correspondence Michigan (State) Department of Labor, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 125)
- General Correspondence University of Michigan, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 126)
- General Correspondence - Individual Middleton, Margaret (Miss), 1956 (Box 16, Folder 127)
- General Correspondence The Militant, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 128)
- General Correspondence Mill and Factory, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 129)
- General Correspondence Individual Mims, Henry N., 1950 (Box 16, Folder 130)
- General Correspondence Miners' International Federation, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 131)
- General Correspondence State of Minnesota, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 132)
- General Correspondence University of Minnesota, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 133)
- General Correspondence University of Mississippi, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 134)
- General Correspondence Modern Industry, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 135)
- General Correspondence Moody's Investors Service, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 136)
- General Correspondence Moore -, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 137)
- General Correspondence - Individual Morrison, Riley A. (Lederie Laboratories American Cyanamid Co., Pearl River, N.Y.) (Box 16, Folder 138)
- General Correspondence Montana State University, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 139)
- General Correspondence - Individual Mullady, Thomas, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 140)
- General Correspondence Individual Mulrooney, Edward P., 1950 (Box 16, Folder 141)
- General Correspondence Municipal Reference Library, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 142)
- General Correspondence Mutual Funds Center, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 143)
- General Correspondence Mutual Insurance 200th Anniversary Committee, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 144)
- General Correspondence "N" "M", 1948 (Box 16, Folder 145)
- General Correspondence "N" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 146)
- General Correspondence "N" Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 147)
- General Correspondence National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 148)
- General Correspondence National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 149)
- General Correspondence National Association of Claimant's Compensation Attorneys, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 150)
- General Correspondence National Association of Manufactuers, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 151)
- General Correspondence National Association of State Universities, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 152)
- General Correspondence National Association of Wool Manufacturers, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 153)
- General Correspondence National Bureau of Economic Research, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 154)
- General Correspondence National Capitol Publishers, Inc., 1951 (Box 16, Folder 155)
- General Correspondence National Child Labor Committee, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 156)
- General Correspondence National Coal Board, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 157)
- General Correspondence National Committee for the Extension of Labor Education, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 158)
- General Correspondence National Council of the Young Men's Christian Associations of the U.S.A., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 159)
- General Correspondence National Dock Labour Board, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 160)
- General Correspondence National Electrical Manufacturers Association, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 161)
- General Correspondence National Emergency Civil Rights Mobilization, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 162)
- General Correspondence National Industrial Conference Board, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 163)
- General Correspondence National Industrial Council, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 164)
- General Correspondence National Institute of Leadership, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 165)
- General Correspondence National Municipal League, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 166)
- General Correspondence National Planning Association, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 167)
- General Correspondence National Publicity Council for Health and Welfare Services, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 168)
- General Correspondence National Religion and Labor Foundation, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 169)
- General Correspondence National Research Bureau, Inc., 1950 (Box 16, Folder 170)
- General Correspondence National Research Center (The), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 171)
- General Correspondence National Retail Dry Goods Association, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 172)
- General Correspondence National Retail Furniture Agency, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 173)
- General Correspondence National Safety Council, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 174)
- General Correspondence National Sales Executives, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 175)
- General Correspondence Note Training Laboratory in, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 176)
- General Correspondence New York Post, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 177)
- General Correspondence New York State, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 178)
- General Correspondence New York State, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 179)
- General Correspondence New York State Department of Labor, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 180)
- General Correspondence New York State Library, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 181)
- General Correspondence New York State Library Gifts and Exchange Section, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 182)
- General Correspondence New York State Library Traveling Libraries Section, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 183)
- General Correspondence New York World Telegram, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 184)
- General Correspondence Newcomb and Sammons, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 185)
- General Correspondence - Individual Neilly, Homer B., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 186)
- General Correspondence - Individual Northup, Herbert R., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 187)
- General Correspondence Norton, W. W. and Co., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 188)
- General Correspondence "O", 1947 (Box 16, Folder 189)
- General Correspondence "O" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence "O" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- General Correspondence Oster's, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- General Correspondence "P", 1949 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence "P" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence "P" Correspondence, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence Parke, Davis and Co., 1955 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- General Correspondence - Individual Pearlman, Mark, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- General Correspondence Plane Designers, Inc., 1958 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- General Correspondence - Individual Poll, John, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- General Correspondence "R" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- General Correspondence "R", 1949 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- General Correspondence "R", 1947 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- General Correspondence "R" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- General Correspondence Ritter Company, Inc., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- General Correspondence Fred B. Rothman Company, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- General Correspondence Fred B. Rothman and Company Special Project, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- General Correspondence Rudge, Fred, Inc., 1958 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- General Correspondence Russell Sage Foundation, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- General Correspondence "S", 1949 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- General Correspondence "S" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- General Correspondence - Individual Schmidt, Godfrey P., 1955 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- General Correspondence - Individual Seidenburg, Jacob, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- General Correspondence - Individual Shaw, Brad, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- General Correspondence Shaw-Walker Company, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- General Correspondence Simmons-Boardman Publishing Corp., 1956 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- General Correspondence Simpson, R. G., and Staff, Inc., 1956 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- General Correspondence Society for Applied Anthology, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- General Correspondence Standard and Poors Corporation, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- General Correspondence - Stanolind Oil and Gas Company, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- General Correspondence Stoller Drug, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- General Correspondence "T" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- General Correspondence "T", 1947 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- General Correspondence Trans World Airlines, Inc., 1956 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- General Correspondence "U" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- General Correspondence "U", 1949 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- General Correspondence Union-Endicott High School, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- General Correspondence - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- General Correspondence U.S. Government Printing Office, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- General Correspondence U.S. Government, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- General Correspondence United States Government, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- General Correspondence U.S. Government, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- General Correspondence U.S. Government, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- General Correspondence Upjohn Institute for Community Research, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- General Correspondence "V", 1948 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- General Correspondence "V" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- General Correspondence Vangorcum, Royal Ltd., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- General Correspondence State of Vermont Public Records Commission, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- General Correspondence Vision, Inc., 1958 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- General Correspondence "W", 1947 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- General Correspondence "W", 1949 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- General Correspondence "W" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 53)
- General Correspondence "W" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- General Correspondence - Individual Wenderlich, Paul M., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- General Correspondence Western Electric Company, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- General Correspondence _ Individual White, Frank Sr., 1955 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- General Correspondence - Individual Wurfel, David, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- General Correspondence "XYZ" Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- General Correspondence "XYZ" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- General Correspondence "XYZ", 1949 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- General Correspondence Yezbak Associates, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- General Correspondence Individual Zaim, Sabahaddin, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Directories - Approved Technical Institutes, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools - General, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools - Colleges Offering Course in Personnel Subjects (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools - American Labor Education Service - N.Y. (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools - California Institute of Technology, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools - California Labor School, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools University of California - Berkeley, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools University of California - Los Angeles, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools University of Chicago, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools - University of Cincinnati, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Colgate University (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Columbia University (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools University of Connecticut, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Cornell University, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Cornell University NYSSILR, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Cornell University NYSSILR, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Cornell University - NYSSILR Federal Labor Union Conference, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Cornell University - NYSSILR Institute on Social Welfare, etc., 1950 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Cornell University - NYSSILR March 1950 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Union Educational Directors Conference, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Labor Market Research, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Trends in Industrial Relations -Student, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Supervisory Training and Human Relations, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Federal Labor Union Institute, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Extension Teachers Conference, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Research Conference March '49, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Research Conference December '48, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Union Research Conference Nov. '48, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Teaching of Labor Economics Aug. '48, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Plant Training Directors July '48, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Labor-Management Conference Aug '47, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Development of Desirable Attitudes, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Dalhousie University, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools University of Denver, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Duquesne University (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Henry George School of Social Science (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools University of Georgia, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Georgia Workers Education Service, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Harding College, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Harvard University, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Management Center-Marquette University, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools University of Michigan, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools University of Minnesota, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Manhattan College, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Universite de Montreal, 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools University of New Hampshire, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools New School for Social Research (Box 18, Folder 51)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools New York State University, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools New York University, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Ohio State University, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Oklahoma A. and M. College (Box 18, Folder 55)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Pendle Hill (Box 18, Folder 56)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Pacific Coast School for Workers, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Hebrew University (Box 18, Folder 58)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Highlander Folk School, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Hobart College - Geneva, New York, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Hudson Shore Labor School, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools University of Illinois, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 62)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Indiana University (Box 18, Folder 63)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Industrial College of the Armed Forces, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 64)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Institute of Applied Arts and Sciences, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 65)
- Iowa University - Bureau of Labor, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 66)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools John Hopkins University, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 67)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Kansas State College (Box 18, Folder 68)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Universite Laval, 1949-1956 (Box 18, Folder 69)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Lehigh University, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 70)
- Universities, Colleges, and Schools Le Moyne College (Box 18, Folder 71)
- Unemployment in the United States, 1900-1952 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Non-Ferrous Metal Mining Industry, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Bibliography A List of Books, Pamphlets and Publications on Marketing, Retailing, Salesmanship, and Merchandising, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Index of Miscellanies and Other Publications, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- International Comparison of Unemployment Rates, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Wage Structure Metalworking Industries, 1945, 1945-1949 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Employment Outlook in Foundry Occupations, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Labor-Management Contract Provisions, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Analysis of Work Stoppages, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Guaranteed Wage or Employment Plans, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Industrial Relations Center, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Industrial Relations Center, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Effects of the Military Draft on Employment in The Iron and Steel Industry, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Suggested Statistical Program Relating to Labor and Industrial Relations Activities in the Iron and Steel Industry, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Statement of Steel Executives, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Salary Adjustment Plans in the Iron and Steel Industry, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Mechanization in the Cement Industry, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- A Working Philosophy of Personnel Management, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Labor - General, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Survey of Group Annuity Plans of Petroleum Industry Companies (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Accounting for the Cost of Pensions -A Lien on Production, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Families Receiving Aid to Dependent Children, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Comparative Analysis, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Collective Bargaining Provisions Incentive Wage Provisions; Time Studies and Standards of Production, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Pensions, social Security Misc., 1947-1968 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Voucher Payroll - Catherwood Library, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Spreadsheets, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Spreadsheets, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- The Times-Union (Albany Time Union), 1963 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- American Association of University Teachers of Insurance, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Association for Latin American Studies ALAS Bulletin, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- ATLAS, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Bernan Associates, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Brookings Institution, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Cornell University Libraries Acquisitions, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Detroit News, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Educational Film Library, 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Group Health Association of America, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- International Council of Industrial Editors, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- International Film Bureau, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- International Ladies Garment Workers, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Iowa State College, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- I.P.C. Distributors, Inc., 1958 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Journal of Inter-American Studies, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Journal of Personnel Administration and Iindustrial Relations, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Kiplinger Letters, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- The Kiplinger Washington Editors, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Kramer, Leon (Bookseller), 1956 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Labor Research Association, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1956-1976 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- League of Women Voters of New York, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Lent's Inc., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Life Filmstrips, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Library of Congress, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Transfer 1951-1956 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Mercury Typesetting Company, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 1)